<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Super.NET</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Super.NET</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 08:58:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/philosophy/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 14:47:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/philosophy/introduction/</guid>
      <description>*[WIP] &amp;ldquo;Introduction to philosophy&amp;rdquo; sounds like a course we&amp;rsquo;re about to take. Well, perhaps it is. I guess we&amp;rsquo;re about to take a course into my philosophy, and I am about to put it in writing rather than having all these thoughts live in my head without paying for rent.
Primarily, this will serve as a guide not only to how I have been thinking about software development &amp;ndash; and indeed, perhaps life itself &amp;ndash; for years now, but it aims to establish how I wish others who may wish to joining at some point to assist in the efforts here to think as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiration</title>
      <link>/philosophy/inspiration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 12:32:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/philosophy/inspiration/</guid>
      <description>*[WIP] The Need for Inspiration In my estimation, the primary issue with our ecosystem is that of inspiration. Note that in my appeal here, I am not suggesting or implying that is a primary aim of this project. I will not complain, however, if that happens to result in a side effect.
Silverlight as an Inspirational Paradigm When I reflect on Silverlight&amp;rsquo;s time, I have to say that I felt more inspired then than at any other time working with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software as a Craft</title>
      <link>/philosophy/craft/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:48:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/philosophy/craft/</guid>
      <description>*[WIP] In the philosophy that is described here, it proposes that software development is a craft, much like wood working, pottery, beer, or &amp;ndash; as this section later calls out &amp;ndash; jewelry.
You Can&amp;rsquo;t Spell Craft without Art I&amp;rsquo;m a bit of a stickler and sucker for words. I enjoy anagrams and things of that nature. If you take the letters a-r-t out of craft, you end up with cf, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Does It</title>
      <link>/philosophy/simple-does-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:52:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/philosophy/simple-does-it/</guid>
      <description>*[WIP] As I mentioned in describing software as a craft, I have been going through a very inspirational time with putting this project together. In this section, I hope to explore a little bit about software design in general and some of the great appreciation that I have acquired by studying Hugo, the very software used to produce and publish the content you are now reading.
Hugo as an Example of Elegance What is so inspiring about Hugo?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 01:42:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Much love and appreciation to the following sponsors who have provided some serious l00t towards reach the goals established here. Especially so since they are really taking a risk in putting their faith in someone who is essentially an unknown.
Super.NET is proudly developed, debugged, tested, and deployed in part by:
ReSharper Ultimate
OzCode
Tower
Code Compare</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 01:41:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/questions/</guid>
      <description> *[WIP] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 01:26:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vision/</guid>
      <description> *[WIP] The Business Problem Cost of Development Principles HTML5 as an Established Presentation Platform Data Formats POICO Development Primary Components Serializer WebSocket Bridge Control Suite Visual Designer </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Culture of Excellence</title>
      <link>/philosophy/culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 01:00:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/philosophy/culture/</guid>
      <description>*[WIP] In our final section here, we examine the ideal culture that we want to build around the philosophy that is being described here. In describing software as a craft, I made a comparison between a &amp;ldquo;one person band&amp;rdquo; and a &amp;ldquo;jeweler,&amp;rdquo; suggesting that we should be striving for more jewelers in the world than one person bands.
In this section, I take this further to demonstrate why the jeweler model is preferred, and why it can lead to our goal as a culture of experts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>